

# Alyasar Jabbarli

Software Engineer | Web Developer

+99450-866-44-55

alyasar.jabbarli@gmail.com

https://github.com/AlyasarJabbarli

https://www.linkedin.com/in/alyasar-jabbarli-813060215/

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a highly skilled web developer, software engineer, and instructor with over 2 years of experience in the tech industry. My expertise lies in building responsive and interactive user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, and I have a deep understanding of popular libraries and frameworks such as React and Angular.

### **LANGUAGES**

- · Russian Native
- English C1
- Turkish B2

## **EDUCATION**

CODE Academy S: "Web Development" 01.2022y. - 09.2022y.

**SABAH Groups** 

BS: "Computer Engineering"(In English)

2021y. - present

Azerbaijan State Oil and Industry University BS: "Computer Engineering"(In Russian) 2020y. - 2021y.

### **SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- AJAX , JQuery
- Bootstrap, Responsive Design, React.JS
- Object Oriented Programming
- C# (.NET Framework, .NET Core);
- ASP.NET MVC;
- ASP.NET Core MVC;
- SQL , MySql;
- Analyzing , Problem Solving
- OS & IT Essential

# **WORK HISTORY**

Project Manager of "Gənc Proqramçıların Təlim Sessiyası" – 11/2022 to 03/2023 Globus Center, Baku, Azerbaijan (https://instagram.com/gpts2023?igshid=YmMyMTA2M2Y=)

- · Developing and leading the team.
- Planning and developing the project idea.
- Establishing a deadline and monitoring the progress of the project.
- · Identifying and resolving issues that arise.
- Preparing budget based on scope of work and resource requirements
- Measuring project performance to identify areas for improvement
- Track project costs in order to meet budget
- Preparing a detailed project plan to schedule key project milestones, workstreams & activities

# Front End Programming İnstructor – 09/2022 to present CELT IT Colleges, Baku, Azerbaijan

- Presenting lessons in a comprehensive manner and use visual/audio means to facilitate learning
- Providing individualized instruction to each student by promoting interactive learning
- Creating and distributing educational content
- Assess and record students' progress and provide grades and feedback.
- · Develop and enrich professional skills and knowledge by attending seminars, conferences etc.
- · Observe and understand students' behavior and psyche and report suspicions of neglect, abuse etc.

# NAYORA IT Committee member– 12/2021 to 04/2022 *Globus Center, Baku, Azerbaijan*

- Participate in training and achieve successful results in them
- Providing Information to the Public
- Preparation of presentations and presenting to large audiences
- •Working cooperatively as a reliable team member to complete assignments
- •Keeping Accurate Records
- Data entry

# Organizing committee member – 11/2021

"Victory Run", Baku, Azerbaijan

- •Helping with Marketing Efforts
- •Other duties specifically around coordination of special events, or as assigned
- Motivating Others to Get Involved
- •Working cooperatively as a reliable team member to complete assignments

# Helpdesk intern – 11/2020 to 02/2021

Crucel LLC, Baku, Azerbaijan

- Assists the Help Desk Team to deliver technology support
- •Keep inventory of all equipment, software, and license users
- ·Assist with onboarding of new users.
- Assist with the deployment of new equipment.
- ·Assist with software installs.
- •Assist in collecting information for the equipment inventory.
- Assist in printer issues.
- Monitor and respond quickly to incoming requests relate to IT issues.

### **VOLUNTEERING & CERIFICATES**

Aquatic Palace Volunteer – 10/2021 Aquatic Palace, Baku, Azerbaijan

iron Wind Volunteer – 10/2021 Pirallahi island, Baku, Azerbaijan

ASAN Service Volunteer -06/2021 to 08/2021 ASAN Service №3, Baku, Azerbaijan

Uniform TM – 05/2021 to 07/2021 Formula 1® group, Baku City Circuit, Baku, Azerbaijan